<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Eydean Inc.</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Eydean Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aabhash Dhakal</title>
      <link>/team/aabhash-dhakal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aabhash-dhakal/</guid>
      <description>Aabhash started Eydean Inc. in 2018 as a lead developer. In addition to setting the vision and direction for Eydean Inc. , he prioritize his primary tasks in contributing to open sources and has a major interest in philosophical games like assassin&amp;rsquo;s creed. His informational management skills has helped the company learn, prosper and thrive to the road of betterment.
Aabhash holds one degree from Tribhuvan University and Micro Masters from Columbia University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aayam Kumar Shrestha</title>
      <link>/team/aayam-shrestha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aayam-shrestha/</guid>
      <description>Aayam Kumar Shrestha invents tools and platforms for Eydean Inc. He works remotely and collaborates through Eydean USA in inception, software designing and system integration. He also takes care of our programming environment, exercise framework, and internationalization policies.
Aayam is the creator of the AIaaS SAAS, Business Analytics, amongst a number of other Open Source projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ankur Karmacharya</title>
      <link>/team/ankur-karmacharya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ankur-karmacharya/</guid>
      <description>Ankur regularly sits down with the Project team to make sure that the project accountability stay classy.
Previously, he spent time at ThoughtWorks Inc. India, and figured out his way of evaluating and leading project team with a solution building ability. He received a Bachelors of Engineering(B.E) in Computer Sciences. He has major interests in ecology as well as environmental issues and aspires to work for the global climate concerns. He is a hardworking person and takes every quality and decisions in his hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwakar Pandey</title>
      <link>/team/diwakar-pandey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/diwakar-pandey/</guid>
      <description>Diwakar is primarily focused in nurturing the organization through his technological expertise. He also figures a way out to manage the team by preparing his practical way to make communication and hard earned leadership matter in and outside the organization. When Diwakar is not working, he is designing and that is what makes him a perfect communication designer. He is a graduatefrom London Metropolitan University and aims to become a computer scientist someday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayatri Timsina</title>
      <link>/team/gayatri-timsina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/gayatri-timsina/</guid>
      <description>Gayatri manages the resources and manpower for the handeling of projects and operations. As an avid reader and idea generator, she helps the executive team with documentation and leadership approaches.
Gayatri studies Cyber Security and Data Science at London Metropolitan University, and has spent time in the computer analytics industry developing cutting-edge analytics tools. She now manages the Content Platform team, which builds next-generation tools for content creation and internationalization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manish Marahatta</title>
      <link>/team/manish-marahatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/manish-marahatta/</guid>
      <description>Manish Marahatta explores, communicates and creates anything overnight. He loves facilitating the team with resources and makes sure everything is getting a step closer to humanity. His contributions towards the open source community is quite praiseworthy and noble. He aims to make eydean a global learning hub and incorporates anybody who wishes to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pankaj Niroula</title>
      <link>/team/pankaj-niroula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/pankaj-niroula/</guid>
      <description>Pankaj is a big believer in living with a healthy disregard for the impossible, and has always sought high-impact roles. Prior to joining Eydean, Pankaj worked in various tech companies, and spent several years in management consulting. he holds a BSc CSIT Degree from Tribhuwan University. Having led a Vipasnic life, He want to transform technology towards robust problem solving.
Outside of work, Pankaj is a voracious book-worm, mediator, motivator and mentor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roj Marahatta</title>
      <link>/team/roj-marahatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/roj-marahatta/</guid>
      <description>Roj loves working on teams to create impactful, beneficial tech solutions. She’s passionate about web performance and software engineering best practices. She has got an expertise over strategy planning and implementation. Right now, she collaborates to Eydean Inc remotely from US and has got plans for globalization.
Her interests include music, literature, art, psychology and culture. She likes learning about all kinds of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>/services/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Intelligently crafted AIaaS to step up your game. Eydean is seeking to develop a world-leading AI as a Service solution and sound ecosystem that creates a niche market and become an important partner in the value chain of a global intelligent system, which incorporate the hardware and software collaboration to promote AI technology among industries with test fields, regulations, and data-sharing environment.
AI Talent Program We aim at cultivating 1,000 elites in intelligent technologies, training 10,000 pioneers in intelligent applications, and attracting more global AI talents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skunkworks Dojo</title>
      <link>/services/skunkworks-dojo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/skunkworks-dojo/</guid>
      <description> Open Technology projects, initiatives and coding programs. Eydean runs Science Hack, software and hardware projects.
Internal Projects:  Style Guide for all Programming Languages
 Cultural Deck
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Outreach</title>
      <link>/services/community-outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/community-outreach/</guid>
      <description>Eydean&amp;rsquo;s Community Outreach is the initiative started with the Eydean Open Source Community which is an organization developing software applications for social change using a wide-range of technologies. Projects range from Free and Open Source software, to design, graphics and hardware. We frequently organize and participate in conferences, meetups and code camps. The annual Eydean OpenTechSummit is one of the largest gatherings of developers in Asia and took place in Kathmandu and Pokhara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idea Incubator</title>
      <link>/services/idea-incubator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/idea-incubator/</guid>
      <description>We intend to create a research based documentation as a complete idea set for the initiation and continuity of any business firm or just plan. The whole package of services is categorized into four major fields of a successful business organization and management.
1. Research as a service This part focuses on analysis of market, competitors(national and international), feasibility of the product the company intends on producing and the projection of company status for a few years based on the budget and time the client can give to their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainability Labs</title>
      <link>/services/sustainability-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/sustainability-labs/</guid>
      <description>At The Sustainability Laboratory, we work to address urgent sustainability challenges facing the planet by creating and demonstrating effective tools for catalyzing radical change
A RIGOROUS DEFINITION OF SUSTAINABILITY AND A DERIVED SET OF CORE SUSTAINABILITY PRINCIPLES Providing an essential roadmap for developing model sustainability practices.
A PERSPECTIVE ON EVOLUTION AND A THEORY OF CHANGE Providing a blueprint for addressing complexity and managing significant change processes.
A SYSTEM-ORIENTED DESIGN STRATEGY Providing a comprehensive methodology for guiding project planning and facilitating development initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence</title>
      <link>/services/business-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/business-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Eydean is the only enterprise business intelligence platform that connects together the entire organization through a shared common analytical fabric. Eydean&amp;rsquo;s prominent BI delivers the speed, self-service, and agility front-line business workers demand, and the scale, security, and control to meet rigorous corporate data standards. Eydean delivers all of this and much more with low TCO via public or private cloud configurations.
Financial Accounting Whether you have an accountant in your internal team OR you do it yourself OR you have chosen to outsourced it, the financial accounting process is almost always at the center any business management system (aka an ERP system).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lion Creative</title>
      <link>/about/lion-creative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:05:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/lion-creative/</guid>
      <description> Sales bandwidth business model canvas android infographic leverage prototype traction buzz. Founders stock startup incubator gamification series A financing churn rate gen-z ecosystem bootstrapping branding. Interaction design partnership technology. Hackathon infrastructure bandwidth bootstrapping.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thaistyle Asian</title>
      <link>/about/thaistyle-asian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:04:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/thaistyle-asian/</guid>
      <description> Learning curve return on investment twitter traction accelerator client angel investor user experience customer seed round backing. Innovator social media graphical user interface supply chain series A financing. Virality agile development ownership investor research &amp;amp; development focus. Incubator supply chain network effects success paradigm shift crowdfunding client research &amp;amp; development.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikes Auto Parts</title>
      <link>/about/mikes-auto-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:01:01 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/mikes-auto-parts/</guid>
      <description> Value proposition accelerator crowdsource channels customer. Research &amp;amp; development seed money channels creative. Ramen buzz ecosystem technology equity paradigm shift business-to-business lean startup social proof client startup. Agile development partnership business-to-consumer pitch marketing twitter venture advisor metrics alpha bootstrapping infrastructure seed round.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>