<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on Eydean Inc.</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on Eydean Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aabhash Dhakal</title>
      <link>/team/aabhash-dhakal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aabhash-dhakal/</guid>
      <description>Aabhash started Eydean Inc. in 2018 as a lead developer. In addition to setting the vision and direction for Eydean Inc. , he prioritize his primary tasks in contributing to open sources and has a major interest in philosophical games like assassin&amp;rsquo;s creed. His informational management skills has helped the company learn, prosper and thrive to the road of betterment.
Aabhash holds one degree from Tribhuvan University and Micro Masters from Columbia University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aayam Kumar Shrestha</title>
      <link>/team/aayam-shrestha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/aayam-shrestha/</guid>
      <description>Aayam Kumar Shrestha invents tools and platforms for Eydean Inc. He works remotely and collaborates through Eydean USA in inception, software designing and system integration. He also takes care of our programming environment, exercise framework, and internationalization policies.
Aayam is the creator of the AIaaS SAAS, Business Analytics, amongst a number of other Open Source projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ankur Karmacharya</title>
      <link>/team/ankur-karmacharya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ankur-karmacharya/</guid>
      <description>Ankur regularly sits down with the Project team to make sure that the project accountability stay classy.
Previously, he spent time at ThoughtWorks Inc. India, and figured out his way of evaluating and leading project team with a solution building ability. He received a Bachelors of Engineering(B.E) in Computer Sciences. He has major interests in ecology as well as environmental issues and aspires to work for the global climate concerns. He is a hardworking person and takes every quality and decisions in his hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diwakar Pandey</title>
      <link>/team/diwakar-pandey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/diwakar-pandey/</guid>
      <description>Diwakar is primarily focused in nurturing the organization through his technological expertise. He also figures a way out to manage the team by preparing his practical way to make communication and hard earned leadership matter in and outside the organization. When Diwakar is not working, he is designing and that is what makes him a perfect communication designer. He is a graduatefrom London Metropolitan University and aims to become a computer scientist someday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayatri Timsina</title>
      <link>/team/gayatri-timsina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/gayatri-timsina/</guid>
      <description>Gayatri manages the resources and manpower for the handeling of projects and operations. As an avid reader and idea generator, she helps the executive team with documentation and leadership approaches.
Gayatri studies Cyber Security and Data Science at London Metropolitan University, and has spent time in the computer analytics industry developing cutting-edge analytics tools. She now manages the Content Platform team, which builds next-generation tools for content creation and internationalization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manish Marahatta</title>
      <link>/team/manish-marahatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/manish-marahatta/</guid>
      <description>Manish Marahatta explores, communicates and creates anything overnight. He loves facilitating the team with resources and makes sure everything is getting a step closer to humanity. His contributions towards the open source community is quite praiseworthy and noble. He aims to make eydean a global learning hub and incorporates anybody who wishes to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pankaj Niroula</title>
      <link>/team/pankaj-niroula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/pankaj-niroula/</guid>
      <description>Pankaj is a big believer in living with a healthy disregard for the impossible, and has always sought high-impact roles. Prior to joining Eydean, Pankaj worked in various tech companies, and spent several years in management consulting. he holds a BSc CSIT Degree from Tribhuwan University. Having led a Vipasnic life, He want to transform technology towards robust problem solving.
Outside of work, Pankaj is a voracious book-worm, mediator, motivator and mentor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roj Marahatta</title>
      <link>/team/roj-marahatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/roj-marahatta/</guid>
      <description>Roj loves working on teams to create impactful, beneficial tech solutions. She’s passionate about web performance and software engineering best practices. She has got an expertise over strategy planning and implementation. Right now, she collaborates to Eydean Inc remotely from US and has got plans for globalization.
Her interests include music, literature, art, psychology and culture. She likes learning about all kinds of things.</description>
    </item>

      <item>
      <title>Manzil Mudbari</title>
      <link>/team/manzil-mudbari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/manzil-mudbari/</guid>
      <description>Manzil currently resides in Crawfordsville, Indiana and leads the sales and business development at Eydean. He is Passionate about making world-class technology developed by Eydean available to businesses around the world. He loves to think deeply about nebulous problems faced by our customers and take initiative to find solutions for that. His goal is to drive the ambitious quest of Eydean on implementing disruptive technological innovation on every aspect of the world. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>